[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elephants spend 16 hours a day collecting and eating food, an average of 400 lbs of food a day. But their bodies do not digest 100% of the food. How much of the food does the elephants body digest?", "correct_answer": "40%", "incorrect_answers": ["80%", "60%", "20%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old must a tree be before it can be tapped for maple syrup production?", "correct_answer": "40 years old", "incorrect_answers": ["30 years old", "10 years old", "20 years old"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the famous American crooner Nat King Cole and his daughter Natalie Cole record their hit song, Unforgettable\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Never", "incorrect_answers": ["in 1989", "in 1990", "The date was never officially revealed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which wedding anniversary is celebrated as Silver Wedding Day by old tradition?", "correct_answer": "25th anniversary", "incorrect_answers": ["35th anniversary", "20th anniversary", "30th anniversary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island, which is a French territory, is located in the Indian Ocean, east of Madagascar, about 200 km southwest of Mauritius.", "correct_answer": "Reunion", "incorrect_answers": ["Saint Denis", "Cilaos", "San Guadalupe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2007 movie Transformers, Bumblebee is an autobot, disguised as what kind of car?", "correct_answer": "A Camaro", "incorrect_answers": ["An 18 wheeler", "A Volkswagen Beetle", "A Corvette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which unit measuring system do 2,240 pounds equal 1 ton?", "correct_answer": "British", "incorrect_answers": ["Avoirdupois", "Both avoirdupois and British", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term blue blood, meaning aristocracy or related to aristocracy, originated in this country.", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Germany", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where would you find the Ore Mountains Euroregion?", "correct_answer": "Czech Republic and Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece and Bulgaria", "Spain and France", "Norway and Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Laurie stab Michael with in the fight scene at the Doyle house in the first Halloween movie?", "correct_answer": "knitting needle", "incorrect_answers": ["scissors", "butcher knife", "chain saw"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In English medieval castles and houses, what room was usually called solar room?", "correct_answer": "A room for solitary activities", "incorrect_answers": ["A room designed for sunbathing", "A room where food was stored", "A room where the family gathered for dinner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does a cat bury his/ her waste?", "correct_answer": "To protect their trail from predators", "incorrect_answers": ["To show their dominance", "Because they are so territorial.", "Because they are very clean animals."]}]